<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Communi help</string>
    <string name="about_community_help_mobile_application_the_community_help_mobile_application_is_a_unique_platform_built_with_the_goal_of_encouraging_kindness_compassion_and_community_driven_support_this_app_is_designed_to_connect_people_who_want_to_offer_help_with_those_who_are_in_need_through_the_donation_and_request_of_essential_items_such_as_second_hand_clothes_useful_products_and_medical_blood_in_many_communities_people_have_items_they_no_longer_need_clothing_that_no_longer_fits_products_that_go_unused_or_the_ability_to_donate_blood_but_don_t_know_where_or_how_to_give_them_to_those_who_could_truly_benefit_at_the_same_time_there_are_many_individuals_in_need_who_lack_a_convenient_trustworthy_way_to_request_such_help_this_app_bridges_that_gap_how_it_works_offering_help_users_can_offer_clothes_household_items_or_medical_blood_to_others_all_they_need_to_do_is_fill_out_a_simple_form_add_a_description_provide_their_contact_information_address_and_phone_number_and_post_the_offer_requesting_help_users_who_are_in_need_can_browse_available_offers_or_submit_a_request_detailing_what_they_need_and_how_others_can_reach_them_direct_communication_the_app_does_not_rely_on_gps_or_map_based_location_tracking_instead_each_offer_and_request_includes_the_user_s_address_and_phone_number_making_it_easy_for_both_parties_to_get_in_touch_directly_and_securely_key_features_clean_and_simple_user_interface_dedicated_sections_for_clothes_products_and_medical_blood_ability_to_post_both_offers_and_requests_browse_offers_by_category_contact_helpers_directly_via_phone_or_address_no_need_for_location_services_or_complicated_sign_ups_the_community_help_mobile_application_aims_to_build_a_network_of_trust_sharing_and_mutual_assistance_especially_in_areas_where_access_to_basic_items_or_emergency_blood_is_limited_whether_you_re_offering_a_helping_hand_or_reaching_out_for_one_this_app_is_here_to_connect_you_with_people_who_care">About Community Help Mobile Application The Community Help Mobile Application is a unique platform built with the goal of encouraging kindness, compassion, and community-driven support. This app is designed to connect people who want to offer help with those who are in need, through the donation and request of essential items such as second-hand clothes, useful products, and medical blood. In many communities, people have items they no longer need—clothing that no longer fits, products that go unused, or the ability to donate blood—but don’t know where or how to give them to those who could truly benefit. At the same time, there are many individuals in need who lack a convenient, trustworthy way to request such help. This app bridges that gap. 👐 How It Works: Offering Help: Users can offer clothes, household items, or medical blood to others. All they need to do is fill out a simple form, add a description, provide their contact information (address and phone number), and post the offer. Requesting Help: Users who are in need can browse available offers or submit a request detailing what they need and how others can reach them. Direct Communication: The app does not rely on GPS or map-based location tracking. Instead, each offer and request includes the user’s address and phone number, making it easy for both parties to get in touch directly and securely. 🌟 Key Features: Clean and simple user interface Dedicated sections for Clothes, Products, and Medical Blood Ability to post both Offers and Requests Browse offers by category Contact helpers directly via phone or address No need for location services or complicated sign-ups The Community Help Mobile Application aims to build a network of trust, sharing, and mutual assistance, especially in areas where access to basic items or emergency blood is limited. Whether you’re offering a helping hand or reaching out for one, this app is here to connect you with people who care.</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>